(Sheldon:)...do you truly believe that you
were ever fit to be a cheer leader?
Look, I just don't think
that the guys and Leonard...
(Penny:)...really meant to hurt you.
They just told an unfortunate lie...
(Penny:)...to deal with a difficult situation.
You know what it's like?
Remember the new Star Trek movie?
Kirk has to take over the ship...
...so he tells Spock stuff
he knew wasn't true.
(Penny:)Like saying Spock didn't care
his mom died.
(Sheldon:)I missed Comic-Con
and the new Star Trek movie?
[SOBBING]
(Raj:)-I like the new look.
-Thanks.
(Howard:)I call it the Clooney.
(Raj:)I call it the Mario and Luigi,
but whatever.
[LEONARD CHUCKLES]
(Raj:)Hey, how's Sheldon doing?
(Leonard:)He came out of his room
wearing his Darth Vader helmet...
(Leonard:)...and tried to choke me to death
with the Force, so I'd say a little better.